[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 52 and height 13?",
      "correctAnswer": "338.0",
      "options": [
        "335.5",
        "338.0",
        "342.0",
        "340.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 56 and height 36?",
      "correctAnswer": "1008.0",
      "options": [
        "1008.0",
        "1010.5",
        "1012.0",
        "1005.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 24 and height 58?",
      "correctAnswer": "696.0",
      "options": [
        "700.0",
        "698.5",
        "696.0",
        "693.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 30 and height 18?",
      "correctAnswer": "270.0",
      "options": [
        "274.0",
        "272.5",
        "270.0",
        "267.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 5 and height 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "17.5",
      "options": [
        "20.0",
        "15.0",
        "17.5",
        "21.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 5 and height 48?",
      "correctAnswer": "120.0",
      "options": [
        "122.5",
        "117.5",
        "124.0",
        "120.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 30 and height 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "135.0",
      "options": [
        "139.0",
        "137.5",
        "135.0",
        "132.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 57 and height 32?",
      "correctAnswer": "912.0",
      "options": [
        "914.5",
        "912.0",
        "916.0",
        "909.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 42 and height 42?",
      "correctAnswer": "882.0",
      "options": [
        "886.0",
        "882.0",
        "879.5",
        "884.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 19 and height 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "85.5",
      "options": [
        "85.5",
        "83.0",
        "88.0",
        "89.5"
      ]
    }
]